Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth.
People tell me my head's in the clouds.
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreaming of you.
You are the treasure I found.
So bright, so bold, it's so elusive.
It's hard to look away.
Even though it's blinding me.
There are no words to
describe how I feel inside.
I'm really, really stuck on you.
I have to follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
And I won't stop till I
get there, you will see.
You're all I need to have
the strength to believe.
Believe in what I do.
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
I'm gonna share them
with you, a love so true.
You're all I want,
together we can move on.
We live how we want to.
There is no limit to us.
We have the power of love.
We don't wanna live ordinary life.
We have a chance to live in paradise.
We believe in one another.
What a nice breeze!
Nami, if you don't mind, I'd
like to stop the ship here.
It'll just be for a
moment. Stop? What for?
I have a very important mission for Karoo.
Karoo?
Karoo, I need you to go to Alubarna Palace
and deliver this letter to my father.
It contains everything
uncovered by Igaran and myself.
The details of Crocodile's nefarious
plans for this country are in here.
Also,
it lets him know that I've returned
to Alabasta safe and sound and
in the company of brave friends
willing to help us in our struggle.
Well, then, can you do this for me, Kaido?
Now, be careful to
conserve your water, okay?
Good luck!
You can do it, Duck!
Go let my father know, Kaido.
There's hope for this kingdom at last.
I said conserve, not consume!
Thank you, and good luck.
Well, I did know the crocodile
was here in Alabasta.
But him trying to steal a kingdom?
That sounds like a bad
joke Because why would a
pirate drop anchor in
one spot and settle down?
Crocodile trying to usurp the throne
of Alabasta doesn't make sense Alright,
let's set this out! Hold on!
You know, there could be another
side to this takeover thing
Huh?
Like some sort of deeper
goal or something.
We're finally here!
Wow, so we're going into the desert?
Does anyone know how hot
it's supposed to get?
Over 100 degrees in the daytime.
What?
Please tell me you're joking!
Ah, Nami, what happened?
Where's your dancer outfit?
Ah, you too!
Vivi, why are you wearing that?
Because any exposed
skin will get sunburned.
You have to cover up in the desert.
But those outfits are so sexy.
Put these on, Luffy. Oh, thank you.
Time to drop anchor. Right.
Yuba, here we come!
What are those?
Turtles?
No, I think they're seals.
Kong Fu Da Gongs!
If you want to come insure,
you'll have to beat me first,
but I doubt that'll happen,
you bunch of cowards.
He says.
Nobody calls me a coward
and gets away with it.
Here comes the pain! No, wait!
Kong Fu Da Gongs are really strong!
See, they're not too tough!
That's bad, too!
What the?
It's one of their rules.
If they lose a Kong fu match,
they become the winner's pupil.
You don't say.
They think you're their master now! Right!
Everyone after me! Now punch!
Now, like this!
Yeah!
Now harder!
And now, lift!
Let's go! Right!
Yeah!
Hope all you guys enjoy the food! See ya!
All you guys. Food.
Now do you get it?
No, they said they wanted to go with
us, so why couldn't we let them?
We don't have the food and water
to take care of a group that big.
Moron.
Honestly,
I don't know what we would have done if
Chopper hadn't persuaded them to stay.
Yeah!
They kept saying, where you
go, we'll follow, Master.
They really would have, too, if
I hadn't given them that food.
And now our food supply's
gotten a lot smaller.
Thanks, Luffy.
Thanks.
He's a handful.
You're telling me.
What's this?
Are we in Yuba already?
No.
Wow.
This is Aramalu.
It was known far and wide
as the City of Green.
It was green?
Take a good look around, everyone.
This is what Baroque Works
has been doing to my country.
The people of Alabasta, this is
what they've had to go through.
Wow, there's nothing
here at all anymore, huh?
No, it's nothing but a ghost town now.
But up until a few short years ago, it
was a thriving city full of gardens,
palm trees, and lush greenery.
This place?
Rain was always scarce here.
But by saving every last drop
of water and using it wisely,
the city was able to make
the foliage flourish.
Unfortunately, that
stopped when the rain did.
Not a single drop of water has fallen in
any part of this country
for three years now.
Three years?
Wow, that long? But wait.
Even without rain, there was still
the river as another water source.
And it's close.
Why couldn't they just pipe
the water in from over there?
Well, the answer to that is just up ahead.
Even though it's a desert kingdom,
never in the thousands
of years of Alabasta's
history has the rain
ever stopped completely.
However,
there was one place in the country
where the rain fell more than usual,
much more in fact.
Alubarna, the capital, the city
where the king's palace is located.
The people of the land
called it the king's miracle.
At least they did until
one particular day.
Get that cargo unloaded!
We've got a schedule to keep!
We're losing it! What happened?
What happened?
Is everyone all right?
Damn it!
What are we supposed to do now?
It's a delivery for the king!
What's he gonna do when
it doesn't arrive on time?
Is green powders for the king?
What is it?
How the hell should we know?
We're only following your king's orders.
We're just couriers.
Run!
Wait a minute.
Could this be?
Dance powder?
Oh, so you've heard of it? Yes.
I sure have.
It summons rain.
A powdered can?
I've only heard stories
about it, But apparently,
dance powder was created by a researcher
in a country where it never rained.
Burning it creates a misty
smoke, which rises into the sky.
Once it reaches the clouds,
it causes them to rain.
In essence, it gives you the
ability to create rain on the spot.
So, in fact, as its name suggests,
the country that developed dance
powder was happy enough to dance.
It got lots of rain.
But there is a catch.
Its neighboring country had a drought.
Let me explain how it works. Now,
the mist from the burned
dance powder targets
small clouds that aren't
ready to rain yet.
It artificially matures
them into full rain clouds.
Those clouds would have
naturally grown into rain clouds,
but when they were further downwind.
Oh, I get it.
It steals all the rain that would have
normally gone to a neighboring country.
That must have caused some big problems.
Oh, it did.
A war broke out between the two countries.
Ever since then,
the world government has
instituted a worldwide ban
on the production and
possession of dance powder.
Even so, some of it managed
to show up here, huh?
When it happened, the country had
been experiencing strange weather.
There had been no rain.
Not a single drop had fallen anywhere
except one place, and that was the capital.
No wonder we haven't had any rain in ages!
The kings stole it from the
capital using this dance powder!
So Alibana's reign wasn't a
miracle at all, it was a sham!
Yeah, one that's left
us parched and starving.
This is all King Cobra's fault.
Vivi!
That means your dad is
the bad guy here! No!
You idiot, he was framed!
Her sweet, dear old dad would
never do such a thing, you got it!
Of course, my father didn't have
anything to do with it, he was innocent.
Unfortunately,
a large amount of dance powder was discovered
inside his palace shortly thereafter.
Huh.
They even had people
working inside the palace.
So, what is this? A road?
No, it used to be a large canal that piped
in fresh water from the Sandora River.
Huh?
Until someone destroyed it.
Now do you see what happened?
With its canal gone,
the city of Green lost its only
remaining source of fresh water.
The people here waited and prayed,
but sadly, rain never came.
Wow,
something like that and
the dance powder incident
would really make people
distrust their king.
That's exactly what
Crocodile planned, I bet.
With no more water, fighting
began to break out in Aramaloo.
To escape the violence here,
there was only one thing the
exhausted citizens could do.
They abandoned the city and left
for other oases in search of water.
And then, the city of Green withered away.
Someone's collapsed!
Wait, you mean there are still
people living in this city?
What did my father and all of the other
good people, what did they ever do?
We don't deserve this.
It's hard enough to live in the desert.
Every day it's a struggle just to survive.
Somehow the people of Alabasta found a
way to do it and they led happy lives.
But Crocodile destroyed those lives.
What gives him the right to do that?
What?
All the while,
as one of the seven warlords, he passes
himself off as a hero of the people.
They don't know what he's really doing.
No one realizes that
he's actually deceiving
the entire country even
as they cheer him on.
Crocodile! Crocodile!
I can't!
I can't let him get away with this!
Oh well.
I hope that made him feel better.
V .V.
Let's get moving, Kay.
I'm itching to do this.
He's right.
Let's get to Yuba.
That's where the Rebel
Army is, right, Yuba?
Yes, I have to stop them.
I'm going to persuade their leader.
How so?
I'll tell the Rebel leader the truth,
that all of this is Crocodiles doing.
And have him stop all of
this pointless bloodshed.
Let's go.
I'm burning up.
I don't think I can even sweat anymore.
Will you please spare us
the melodramatics, Luffy?
You're only going to wear yourself out.
Gee, I guess he's not listening.
I can't go on.
I can't take hot weather.
I'm fighting cold weather.
It's because of all that fur.
Why don't you take off that
stupid reindeer costume?
What did you just say to me? Red nose!
Don't make fun of reindeer! MONSTER!
Chopper, don't turn yourself big
or I'm going to quit pulling you.
Who are you calling a
monster, you bird-nosed freak?
You better take it easy on the
nose or I'll have to get topped.
Turn small, will ya?
Hey, the desert doesn't seem
to bother you much, Phoebe.
Well, I was born and
raised in this country,
so I guess you could say I'm used to it.
So, what's with all these hills?
I was expecting a desert to be more flat!
This is a very old desert.
Some of the sand dunes here are
over 900 feet high. 900 feet?
Oh my god, no!
That's...
That's a mountain!
No hot water!
Just one drink, Luffy.
Just one mouthful.
Don't drink so much! Idiot!
You'd better save some
of that water for Usa!
Hold on, you just had some odd kicks!
Give me that kick!
Stop it, you guys!
You're only going to wear
yourselves out if you keep it up!
Hey, she started it!
It's your fault!
It's always his fault!
Hey, Sanji, let's have one of
those box lunches. Not yet.
Not until Vivi says so.
Come on, Vivi, how about it?
Let's eat!
Doesn't that sound good?
But we're not even a
tenth of the way to Yuba,
Luffy, and we have to make our
supplies last the whole way.
Don't be silly, Vivi.
Haven't you heard the old proverb?
Make sure you eat whenever you're hungry.
Oh, quit making things
up, you big fat liar.
Okay, if you're that
hungry, I'll tell you what.
Why don't we stop and eat at the
next group of rocks we come to?
All right, rocks it is.
Onward to the next group of rocks.
Okay, guys, whoever wins at rock, paper,
scissors has to carry everybody's stuff.
Quit deciding things.
And ready, go. No! Rock! Paper! Wait!
No, just hold on!
Hey, you started late!
I win! Idiot.
Heavy.
So heavy.
Why am I doing all the work?
You said the winner carries all.
Now shut up and haul!
Make sure you don't drop anything!
Hey, guys!
I spotted Rockstead ahead!
You mean it!
It's lunchtime!
Whoo!
That's so fast!
Oh, shade.
It feels so good.
I need help!
That's weird.
Why is he coming back?
There's a whole flock of injured
birds here that can't move!
We need a doctor! Chomper!
All right, let's go, Chomper! Coming!
We gotta help those birds! What
birds? Wait a minute, Luffy!
Those birds might not be
what you think they are!
Huh?
All of our stuff is gone.
We've been had.
But I saw them!
There was a whole flock of
dying birds lying right there!
I'm so sorry.
I should have mentioned this earlier.
What do soggy birds
are desert bandits that
deceive travelers and
steal their belongings?
You gotta be kidding!
You mean these birds play dead?
What a lousy bunch of crooks!
This is all my fault.
Those birds tricked me!
Luffy, you dolt, is that all
you have to say for yourself?
There were three days'
worth of supplies in those packs,
and you just had to go
and let a bunch of stupid
birds rob us blind in
the middle of a desert.
How are we supposed to get across
this wasteland without food or water?
I hope you're proud of yourself.
Come on, it's not my fault.
I mean, they outsmarted me.
You mean you're dumber than a bird?
What's that?
Knock it off, you two.
No, you're not that smart!
Just save your energy.
At times like this, it's better
just to let them have it out.
You're such a moron!
You are for what am I?
Fine with me.
Let's just take a break.
This heat is just starting to
wear on everybody's nerves.
I'm sure we'll manage food and water wise.
It's nothing that'll kill us right away.
Let's put it out of our minds for now.
Yeah, that's a good idea because when
I think about it, I get really thirsty.
Ah!
Gennosaurus, jump back in there!
No, Luffy!
Don't chase them!
That idiot. Wait!
Will you be able to find your way back?
Get back here, you dope! Luffy!
Stop!
You can't get away from me!
Get back here!
Come on, Luffy.
Hurry it up.
Um, you don't suppose he
could be lost, do you?
There are still so many desert dangers I
haven't had a chance to warn him about yet.
What's that?
What on earth is that rumbling?
Is it another sandstorm?
No, wait, that looks like...
It's Luffy!
Oh no, it can't be.
Huh?
Why is he on a camel?
Someone want to tell me
what the hell's chasing him?
I can't really tell,
but it looks like there's something
in the sand burrowing after him.
What is that?
It's a Sandora Dragon! It's a what?
A Sandora Dragon!
They're the biggest reptile
that lives in the desert.
They wait under the sand for
their prey and then ambush them.
They have razor-sharp fangs and
claws, but they hardly ever use them.
Because they're so incredibly huge,
they usually just end up
swallowing their victims whole!
I gotta admit that boy
does have a talent for
attracting trouble
right and all of us have
the scars to prove it
What kind of crap star
was he born under to
attract trouble like that?
You didn't have to go that far.
Whenever those guys fight, it almost
makes me feel sorry for the monsters.
Is this convenient?
These rocks are just like
a natural frying pan.
So, now that we have a moment, what's
the deal with the camel? I don't know.
It was getting eaten by the mystery
plants while I was chasing those birds.
It's obviously not a wild camel.
No, not with a saddle and bridle.
He's a passenger-carrying camel.
That's sure going to
make things a lot easier.
Yeah, that ought to be a real help.
It looks like he could carry two.
Camels do go hand-in-hand with deserts.
Great, I'll take the first shift.
Ow!
I'm a freedom-loving, hard-boiled,
yet compassionate son of the desert.
I'm very grateful to you for having
helped me out of that jam back there?
And I'll be glad to
give some of you a ride,
but I'm afraid I don't
accept male passengers.
I'm too macho.
I'm so sorry that my crewmates
are a bunch of ill-bred louts.
Now, what should we call you, you
great big precious gamble, you?
Idiot! Moron! Doofus!
Eyelash it is, then.
Uh, how'd you arrive at that?
Okay, climb on, Vivi.
No, I'm fine. I can still walk. Thanks.
Just get on. Pervert camel.
Pervert camel.
This is great.
We should be able to make better time now.
We need to get to Yuba as fast as we can
so we'll be able to talk to the Rebel Army.
Giddy up, Eyelash.
Hey, wait for us.
Hurry up, guys.
If you get separated, you'll
never leave the desert alive.
Well, thanks a lot.
I like this side of Nami, too.
What else is new?
After them, hurry! Chopper, hop on!
Wait for us!